- Barry.
- Hi, Stuart.
Do you think Barshens has any talent?
I don't know. Maybe we should do a video to find out.
No.
[theme music]
- Wow, what an amazing set of credits!
- [Stuart gasps]
We've blown the budget out of the water!
But don't...not really...it doesn't stop there, does it? Oh, no.
- We haven't actually blown the budget out of the water. Thank God for that.
- No, no. No. Phew.
Uh, we have sourced from the crew, the Barshens crew, some of the best talent around.
- Mmm.
- And it's not about us, it's about them.
- It's all about them...
- Yeah.
- ...and how rude we can be to them after they've bared their soul to us.
- Mmm-hmm.
You're going to be the rude one, I'll be the nice one, or do you...
I think we should just, uh, be honest, by which I mean we'll both be rude.
- [Paul laughs off-screen]
- Yeah? And there are no prizes.
Yeah, no prizes, except...
- the adulation of the masses...
- Hmm.
- A worship.
- which is in itself...
worthless.
- [Stuart] Hello.
- [Ryan] Hello.
- [Barry] Hello.
Hello, my name is Ryan, I'm from Norwich...
[Stuart] We know, mate, you've worked here for like years.
Who have you come here today with, Ryan?
- Stuart and Riyad on...on the train.
- [Paul laughs off-screen]
- [Barry] Oh, yeah.
- [Stuart] Yeah.
- [Barry] What else didn't we ask?
- [Stuart] Umm...yeah...
[Stuart] Do you have a sob story?
Any sob story we can play on and then...edit up.
Four days before my eighth birthday, my pet hamster, Thomas, died.
My mum told me in the bath, and I cried, and said he was selfish.
- Ah.
- [Stuart laughs] He was!
- It's a selfish fucking hamster.
- Yeah.
[Barry] Well, I'm sure he'd be proud of you today, Ryan.
- He's looking down on you.
- Yeah.
He's dead.
All right. Do your thing, then. [clears throat]
What...what is the nature of your act?
Um, so, I'm...Have you seen the film Pitch Perfect?
- [Ryan] Either of you.
- [both] No.
[puts chair down] I'm actually really fucking nervous.
- [Stuart] I'm not surprised. That's a glass, isn't it?
- [Barry] Just...just take your time, Ryan.
Just take as long as you need.
- [Stuart] I'm intrigued as to where this is going.
- [Barry] Might as well...
- It might take me a little...
- [Barry] Yeah, take your time. Take your time.
Okay.
[Ryan makes a beat with his hands and the glass]
[singing] I got my ticket for the long way 'round
[emotional music starts] Two bottle of whiskey for the way
and I sure would like some sweet company
and I'm leaving tomorrow, what do you say?
When I'm gone, when I'm gone
You're gonna miss me when I'm gone
You're gonna miss me by my hair
You're gonna miss me everywhere
Oh, you're gonna miss me when I'm gone
[Barry] Whoo!
- [Applause]
- [Paul] That was very good!
- [Barry] Good job!
- Yeah. I'm gone. I'm gone. Sorry.
- Barry's teared up.
- Uh, sorry.
- Barry actually has teared up.
- Yeah, uh...
[Barry] Your hamster is looking down on you, Ryan. That was...[sniffles]
[Stuart] Yeah.
That was really good. Yeah. Be proud. Sorry.
[emotional music stops] I thought it was shit. Fuck off.
[Paul laughs off-screen, Barry giggles]
[silence]
Off!
[Paul] Aww. Round of applause, though.
[Applause]
[Barry] It was a "yes" for me.
But the head judge took the "no".
- [Barry] You're the head judge.
- [Ryan] Fuck...you.
[out of breath] Thank you.
Hello.
- [Stuart clears throat] Hello, Paul.
- [Barry] Hello.
- [Paul] Hello.
- [Barry] What's your name, Paul?
My name's Paul. I'm from Liverpool and, uh...
I like the colour red...
and...my favourite singers are Sonia and Cilla Black.
- [Stuart snickers] Wow. If only they dated.
- Yeah.
- [Stuart] Umm, what's your sob story, Paul?
- [Paul exhales]
I exist.
- [Stuart] Ooh. That...you got me right there.
- Yeah?
- [Paul] My very existence...
- Right on the microphone.
- [Paul] ...is painful.
- [Paul] Uh...but...uh...
- [quietly] It's all right, Barry. It's all right.
- Okay, sorry.
- [Barry] Take as much time as you need.
- [Stuart] Yes, as long as it's not more than five minutes.
[Paul] Well, before we go any further, I need to give you something.
- [Barry] Mate...
- So, I've got this...
- [Barry] Okay.
...right? And I need you to put this in your top pocket, where it's safe, right?
So, there you go, and I'm not going to be able to touch that the whole time, okay?
- [Barry] Okay.
- [Paul] All right?
- So, I'll begin, [sniffles] okay? [sniffles]
- [Stuart clears throat]
I'm not...sorry, I just want to...
I just want to...Before we get going, I've got a little bit of hay fever, so let me just, uh...
have some of this, and then I'll just, uh...
It's gone. So, that's my first trick.
[in awe] Aww! What?
- [Barry laughs]
- All right. So...my next trick...
uh, involves these three balls...
and these three cups, right?
Here we go. I'm going to take one little ball, right? This, I'm going to put on top of this little cup here,
and then I'm going to do that, and...
The magic words are "Piffity Puff Puff". [laughs] Right?
- I thought it might be.
- So, after one, two, three, say "Piffity Puff Puff" with me.
- One, two, three...
- [all three] Piffity Puff Puff!
And look. Oh, ooh, no, there we go.
- [Barry wheezes]
- [Paul] There we go.
There's the first ball.
And then we're going to put this on here like that... [laughs]
Why is everything I do shit?
- All right. One, two, three...
- [all three] Piffity Puff Puff!
- And look. There we go.
- [Stuart gasps]
- We've got two balls now.
It's getting better and hotter, isn't it?
- Right.
- [Stuart, quietly] He likes balls.
And then, the final...the final ball goes onto the cup like that,
I give the old magic words. One, two, three,
[all three] Piffity Puff Puff.
And look! Oh, it's three balls! One, two, three!
It's magic!
Right. [sniffles] Now, ...
- [Paul] ...finally...
- [quietly] Ooh, there's more. There's more.
...for my last magic trick, I'm going to get three ob--objects chosen at random that I picked ages ago.
So, I...have got this, and this is for Barry, okay?
- [Barry] Okay.
- So, I've got three objects.
All I want, Barry, from you, right now, is to pick any two of these objects out. Which do you fancy?
The crown...
and the water.
Right, cool.
Right. Now...pick me one of these.
- The water.
- You want the water.
- Yeah.
- Can you look in your top pocket then, please?
And tell me what it says written on that pocket piece of paper.
[Barry giggles]
- Oh, this is...do I need to show it to the camera? I think...
- [Paul, quietly] Yeah.
[in awe] Aww!
- [Paul] It says "bottle of water", ladies and gentlemen!
- [Stuart gasps]
[Paul] I am magic. That's been my act.
I wish I had a proper girlfriend.
Well done! That was, uh...
[Applause]
Yeah.
[Paul] I am magic.
Are you classically trained, Paul?
I am, but not in magic.
[Barry laughs] I was very impressed by that.
- [Paul] Yeah, uh, were you impressed by that?
- Does that blow your mind, you know, when he did that?
I thought that was absolutely pathetic. You made a joke of yourself. Get off the stage.
- [Barry laughs]
- Yay, I did well! I did really well!
Bye!
[Applause]
- [Stuart] Hello, Chris.
- [Barry] Hello, Chris.
- [Chris] All right.
- [Barry laughs]
- Where are you from, Chris?
My name's Festival Twat, I'm 39, and I'm from the Wirral.
- Amazing.
- Wow. What are...what are those things dangling? They look like big earrings.
These are...these are fire poi, so, basically, you have to imagine that these are sort of a...
a roaring inferno and we're currently...
burning YouTube Space down.
- Okay.
- Okay. I'm getting on board with that. Yeah.
- Yeah.
When do we do that?
It's...it's in your mind, man, so you've just got to...
[Barry] Okay. [laughs]
- ...go with it, ...
- [Barry] That's good. Yeah, yeah.
- ...go with it...
Let it burn.
- Okay, yeah.
- Uh, what's your sob story?
My cat's very sick.
- That sounds pretty...
- Yeah.
- ...pet related.
- Are you hoping that the...the prize will help...?
- Yeah.
- The prize were stronger, though, to be fair, the pet was dead, and not...
- Oh...
Uh, I mean, it can be dead, if that helps.
- Umm...
- [Chris] Would that help? I can do it now.
- When did you last check it was alive?
[Chris] I can do it now, it's...
- Umm...
- I've got it in a box outside, it's no problem.
[Stuart] Do it afterwards, and then we'll say we did it before.
- All right. With a brick, is that all right? I mean...
- I don't care how.
- [Stuart] Right...
- Awesome!
- [Stuart] So, what is your act?
Well, it's fire poi. I might start fires myself, but only in my mind, so that's okay.
- [Stuart] Do your thing.
- This is basically all I can do, because I haven't done it for about ten years.
[ominous music starts]
I'm going to attempt a trick which will most likely result in me twatting myself in the face.
- [Chris] ...For your entertainment.
- Okay.
Yeah, that...that's a strong proposition.
Uh, this is the 5-beat weave...
...and I used to be really good at it, and now I'm really shit at it, ...
...but if you can imagine the flames, it will add a sense of peril, and I believe that will help...
...me walk off with that prize and possibly a living cat.
I mean, to be fair, I could have just imagined a trick and not had anybody on.
- [Barry] Oh.
- [Stuart] Whoa. Whoa. Watch the mic.
- There we go. There's the windmill.
- [Barry] Ah.
[Applause]
[Paul] Whoo!
- And now, we're all on fire.
- [Stuart] Ooh.
- [Barry] Ah.
[Barry] Wow. Can you put the fire out now, or...?
- No, that's it. We're fucked. We're burned.
- [Barry] Okay. [giggles]
Umm...ah, that was very impressive.
[ominous music stops]
Ah, I thought it was dated, worthless, and get off.
[Stuart] Eli Rolls!
- [Stuart] He's blown...he's blown his load early.
- [Barry] Yeah, Mr Man of Silver, Eli.
Hi!
- [Stuart] Hello.
- [Barry] Hello.
[Stuart] Oh, good, he's got the energy going. This is going to be bad.
[Barry] Nice shirt.
- So, uh...where are you from, Eli?
- [Eli laughs]
Sorry, I'm...just thinking about how my act's going to be...rocking!
- Uh...
- [Barry and Paul laugh]
Where am I from? From London.
- And what's your sob story, Eli?
- [Eli] I have...
...blotchy upper arms.
- [Eli] ...maybe.
- A bit weaker, I feel, that one.
- [Eli] Well, no, no.
I might have to cut gluten out, and it could help.
[Barry] Oh, okay.
Probably the biggest tearjerker story we've had today, to be honest.
- They're well blotchy, man.
- [Barry, disappointed] Yeah.
[Paul laughs off-screen]
- What's your act?
- What is your act, mate? Yeah.
Now...I have...
[coughs] ...an interpretive dance...
...with a little bit of a dialogue, a little drama...
...mixed with dance. Uh...
Could this be described as physical poetry?
[Eli] That's exactly what it is.
It's so nice to meet a judge who actually knows about, you know, the, uh...the definition of art forms.
So...[clears throat]
[opens jar] This is Keith...
[Paul laughs]
[sniffs] Ooh.
- Uh...
- [Barry] What is Keith?
He...he is a mummified mole.
- Yes, he really is, isn't he?
- Oh, my God! [laughs]
- [Stuart] Yeah!
- [Barry] Is it actually a mole?
- Yeah.
- [Stuart] It was at one stage, yeah.
- [Stuart] That's a very dead mole.
- [Barry] Oh, wow!
Was it...was that found in the crawl space of a building? Or, uh...?
I'm not sure. It was given to me...
...by, uh...
...Ryan's parents, so...
[Paul howls with laughter]
And I will...
...symbolically birth...
[Paul laughs]
- ...Keith...
- [Stuart] Okay, yeah.
...and then he will have a dialogue...
[Paul laughs]
...with this artificial cabbage flavour instant vermicelli noodle.
- Why artificial cabbage? Cabbage isn't hard to get, is it?
- [Barry laughs]
- [Eli] Yeah.
- There's something wrong with that, yeah.
Well, it's from a province in China where they had a...
...cabbage drought. [laughs] Sorry.
- [Barry laughs]
- Ah...that province.
- Yeah.
- Okay?
- [Barry] Yeah, whenever you're ready. Take your time.
- All right. Thanks.
Just let us know when you're ready.
- Okay, I'm ready.
- Are you ready? [laughs] Yeah?
[dramatic music starts]
[Eli makes pain sounds to simulate childbirth]
Keith...
Keith...!
I've borned you!
Now Keith is walking along!
[Eli and other people laugh]
What's that?
Keith...Keith, what's that?
What's that?!?
He says it's a noodle.
[laughter continues]
He says it's a noodle!
Shall we go over there? Yes.
I've borned you.
[sniffs]
Smells artificial. Why don't you ask it what it is, Keith?
Okay.
Mr Noodle?
Yes?
[Barry giggles]
What flavour are you?
Artificial noodle,
and cabbage and fish.
I hate fish.
That makes me angry.
[Eli as Keith growls]
[dramatic music becomes more intense]
[shouting] Angry Keith!
What happens to angry Keith? He shows his true face!
The other side of Keith: the witch side!
[Barry giggles]
The witch mouth of Keith's anus!
ARGH!!!
He strangled his maker! Argh!
[making choking sounds]
[Applause] [Paul] Oh, amazing. [dramatic music stops]
[Barry cackles]
[Eli] Thanks.
[various people laugh]
[laughter quiets down]
- [Stuart] Well, what did you think, Barry?
- One of the quietest performances of the day.
- Cheers, understated.
- Yeah.
- [Eli, quickly] So, am I through to the next round?
[Barry sighs] Umm...
My dad says I'm...I'm the best.
- Yeah.
- [Eli] I'm the best.
He says I'm the best.
When I came out of my mum, he said I'm the best.
- He said I--I'm going to be the..."you're going to be the best".
- Well...
The best dead mole wrangler ever.
I mean...in a dead mole category, you're probably winning it today.
- [Stuart] Yeah.
- [Barry] We've got a winner.
- I'm through to the next round! Dad!
- [Stuart] No. No, you are not. Back.
- [Stuart] Yeah, I mean...
- [Barry] So we can't...
Uh...it started strongly, I'll give you that, ...
- [Stuart] ...but then, the tonal shift was too great.
- [Barry] Hmm.
Uh...the witch anus...
the witch mouth anus...was just too much of a combination, I feel.
- [Barry] Hmm.
- [Stuart] Uh, overall...
- [Barry] That's the first time we've had a witch anus act.
...it's the worst thing I've ever seen, and I saw...
the Keith Lemon film at the cinema.
[Paul] Oof.
- Maybe come back next year.
- No, don't.
- Okay. [Paul laughs off-screen]
- But we're quite interested in seeing the mole again.
- All right.
- I'm changing, sir.
- [Stuart] Yeah, that's fine. All right. [Ryan laughs off-screen]
We'll get, uh...Ant & Dec to stick you on the mole list. Right.
And don't forget, if you'd like to apply for Barshens' Got Talent next year...
Yeah, don't bother!
'Cause, uh...there ain't going to be one.
Bye!
[theme music]
[silence]
What are you doing? [laughs]
Oh, all right, okay. Reacting to a...
Yes. Thank you, Barry. [both laugh]
I thought you were actually having an indigestion!
[Barry cackles]
[Eli] Where's my noodle?