[Chris] Welcome to Barshens, and this is a quiz called "Be Careful What You Wish For"!
Shall we talk about what...what you guys wish for, or shall we just crack on?
Umm...you could do.
- What...?
- It depends if you think the format needs a bit of extra padding at the start.
- It might do, to be fair.
- Mmm.
- Okay, okay.
- What do you wish for?
- I wish for...
...peace on Earth...
- Sounds...
- ...and goodwill to voles.
Hmm. What about you?
I wish to go on the Jurassic Park ride at Universal Studios.
[male voice] Barshens.
[Chris] Are you guys familiar with the concept of Wish?
- Oh, Wish.com!
- [Ryan] None.
[Barry] Ah!
[Stuart singing] They sell you tat for cheap!
[Chris] Anything you could imagine, and I mean...
[Chris] ...anything...
[Barry] Okay.
[Chris] ...exists on Wish.
[Stuart] Eli's...beans?
[Eli] My beans exist in China.
[Chris] What we're going to have is a bunch of things that I've found on the Wish website, and the idea is, you have to...
...guess what its purpose is. Simple as that.
And also, you have your...Speed Knob card...
- [Stuart] Oh.
- If you could pass these out...
[Ryan] Why has mine got pubes, and the others' haven't?
[Eli] You've got a pointy pee-pee.
[Stuart] Problematic.
And...there's something going on with the testicles there, I don't like, as well.
[Chris] One of the items from Wish may or may not be a sex toy...
- [Ryan gasps]
- If you think before your...
Before you guess that that's the sex toy...
play your Speed Knob card, and that's a chance for you to get an extra bonus point.
[Chris] Shall we do the quiz?
[Stuart] Please.
[man whispering sensually] Wish.
[Chris] Fucking hell!
[Stuart] Well, this is comfortable.
[Eli] Squeezy. [Stuart grunts]
[Ryan] Hang on.
[Chris] This is...uh, six examples of the same item.
[Stuart] Yeah.
[Stuart] I think both me and Barry know what this is.
[Barry] Yeah.
You put that on a saucepan...
...on the lip of it, and it lets some steam go out, put the...lets the lid rest on it.
Why would you...? Well, just take the fucking lid off!
- [Stuart] Yeah...
- You can have it so it's just hanging, it just gives it a little bit of support.
[Stuart] It's a novelty gift thing, for people who like cooking, you see?
- You like what? Letting a bit of steam, but not all the steam off.
- Yeah.
[Chris] It's not what they're advertising it for, because, umm...
This sort of weird sex party...
...of little tiny men was basically another clue.
[Barry] Right.
- But your answer is that's their primary purpose, so now...
- Yeah. Like...like that, yeah?
Basically, I've fucked it already, haven't I?
[Paul, off-screen] Welcome to the fold. You've fucked everything.
[Chris laughs]
[Stuart] Welcome to Barshens! You obviously haven't been listening when you've been recording the sound!
[Barry] Should I play my sex card? I'm sorry, I'm confused.
- There's a twist.
- Does anybody want to have a guess of another purpose that these could be used for,
which is what it's primarily being sold as, on Wish?
[Ryan] Uhh...coat hanger.
[Barry] Human Centipede...
[Barry] Human Centipede...replica.
[Chris] It was primarily...
[Eli] Chopstick holder!
[Chris] ...on Wish being sold as a chopstick holder,
[Chris] ...but, since I fucked it...
[Stuart] Oh!
But it doesn't really work as a chopstick holder! What a bizarre thing!
[Chris chuckles]
- Welcome to Wish!
- [Stuart] Yeah.
- Points all rounds!
- [everyone cheers] Yay!
[Barry] Chopsticks are sexy.
[Ryan] Right.
[Stuart] Okay.
[Eli] Next one.
[Chris] Next one...
[man whispering] Wish.
[Chris] This is just a oner...it's not very difficult. What do you think that is?
[Ryan] I think you put...your fingers and thumbs in it, and you...
[Stuart] Yeah, as like an exerciser.
[Ryan] ...stretch it. Yeah.
[Eli] Finger exerciser.
[Ryan] I think so.
So, for people who are going to go and present children's programs, with glove puppets.
[Eli] Is it fake chewing gum?
[Ryan snickers]
How? Could you talk us through the process of it?
You put it in your mouth, you chew it, spit it out when you're done, give it a rinse.
- What's the purpose of the hole?
- [Barry mumbles]
The hole is, you can stick your tongue through it.
- Yeah.
- It's a tongue trainer.
[Barry] I reckon you carry beer bottles with it.
[Eli] Yeah, beer bottles.
[Eli] You stick a bunch of beer bottles through it, and then you can carry a bunch...
Oh, no, 'cause it...there's no bit to hold it as a handle by.
[Ryan] No...I think.
[Paul, off-screen] I love the fact that you've lost all will to live, and it's only, what? Two questions? [Chris and Ryan laugh]
[Stuart] No, fifty-eight!
[Paul] You really excelled!
[Chris] That is...[clicks laptop touchpad] two points for Ryan and Stuart.
[Chris] And disturbingly...
[Barry] "Lover-Beauty Best"...
[Stuart] Oh.
[Chris] It's a bit sexy, but it's not really a sex toy.
[Paul] No.
[man whispering] Wish.
[Eli] It's a rubber chicken...
- ...and it makes a squeaky noise, and it's for a dog.
- [Barry] Dog toy, yeah.
[Stuart] I think it is, indeed, obviously a fake chicken, you can't deny that bit, but I think it's an electronic one.
I think you press the button and it makes chicken noises or squeaks electronically.
- There's...a thing around its neck, so you can take the head off.
- [Barry] Yeah.
[Ryan] I was going to say it's like for seasoning...seasoning a chicken and you put some stuff in there, maybe put it...
Ryan's got two points!
[Eli] For what?
[Stuart] Hey!
[Ryan, incredulous] Fuck off!
[Barry] Hey!
[Stuart] Oh, my God!
[Chris] You didn't need the second picture.
[Eli] What is it? A herb...?
[Chris] It's actually called...the "Crock Coq".
The Crock Coq! Oh-ho-ho-ho!
[Eli] What? You stick it in, you stick the herbs in, and then you can take the herbs out and it might save...?
[Ryan] That's great!
[Barry] Yeah, to add the flavour in. Yeah.
[everyone else] Yeah.
[Eli] Imbue their flavour into your dish.
[man whispering] Wish.
[Barry] Oh! [Stuart] Oh.
[Barry] That, is a...
[Eli] I know what that is.
- I know what that is.
- [Chris] Do you want to hold...
- [Barry] Is that...? Oh, uh...
Yeah, I'm going to chuck this in.
[Stuart, shocked] Oh, no! Oh, no! It's not, is it?
[Chris] Interesting!
[Ryan gasps]
[Chris] Do you want to walk us through that?
[Barry] I think that's a "wankerchief".
Oh, my God.
- I think that's a Wankerchief...
- It could be.
- [Stuart] No, 'cause, uh...
where somebody puts their stem around it, ...
...and then...and they release their pollen...
[Paul laughs off-screen]
...after agitating the stem,
[Stuart] Yeah.
[Barry] ...and then, the pollen is collected in...the handkerchief, the Wankerchief.
[Stuart] No. I'm not agreeing with this.
[Eli] That is...
[Chris coughs]
[Eli] That is for solo...
hair and face shaving.
And it collects the hairs.
- [Chris] I mean, that's quite big for a wank.
- You stick your head through there, and it collects the hairs.
- Yeah, that's exactly...
I did wonder at first if it was some sort of evil sex swing, but I noticed those small suction cups...
would not hold the weight of a human.
[Ryan] So, I th--I think this goes on the mirror,
[Stuart] Yeah.
[Ryan] ...and your barber, or yourself, cuts your hair, and it all falls...
[Barry] I think you're right!
[Ryan] ...into the...
[everyone laughs]
[Eli] You cannot take...You can't take your...that!
[laughter]
[Eli] Two points each?
[Chris] One point for everyone, except Barry, who's disgusting.
[Barry] Oh, no.
[Chris] It is, in fact...a shaving...
[Eli] I was the first to say that.
[Barry] The Wankerchief is a good invention, though.
[Paul, off-screen] It is!
[Barry] Yeah.
[Eli] What's the Wankerchief?
[Chris] Like that, but you put your dick through it.
[Barry] Well, we just invented it, didn't we?
- You put that around your "schtem"...
- [Chris laughs] Your "schtem".
And then you put your suckers on the wall, so you've got a good surface area, and then...
[Ryan] Barry. Your...your agent right now is just...
[Barry laughs]
[man whispering] Wish.
[Stuart] Oh. [Ryan] They look like...p--punctured testicles.
[Eli] Ear warmers.
[Chris] This is, again...it's for one point, and there's only one picture for this.
[Eli] Kidney warmers.
[Stuart] Umm...
[Ryan] Hmm.
[Stuart] They could be...um...
Giant golden beans.
Kind of look almost like a prosthetic, you sort of put on, then put make-up over, but I don't think so.
[Stuart] They could be, like, pads you put in your shoes, if your shoes are uncomfortable.
[Eli] Yes.
[Eli] They look like that sort of thing, don't they?
[Stuart] Under the...the ball of the foot.
Would they be that small, though?
- Oh, yeah, they're tiny!
- [Barry] Like a heel protector.
- For people with really small feet. Yes.
[Eli] Eyebrows.
Yeah...?
Flattened banana.
[Stuart] Flattened bananas, that's what they are.
[Stuart] Like...designer bananas.
[Eli] Golden flattened banana flakes.
Answers?
Flattened banana cake!!!
Stu?
[Stuart] Umm...I think they are s--for protecting, like, part of your hand...?
[Ryan] These are ear protectors for when you go swimming.
[Barry] Is that the right answer?
[Chris] They're all...they're all lovely answers, and they're actually all a lot more sensible than reality, which is...
[Barry] Ah!
[Stuart] Oh.
[Barry] I think...
[Eli] And they're for, like, night cream.
[Chris] Yeah.
You put them onto your eyes and they make you look intensely startled, and...
[Barry] A bit like a superhero.
[Eli] No, it's for...to stop the bags developing.
[Stuart] Oh. That probably does nothing.
[Chris] No, they do absolutely nothing.
[man whispering] Wish.
[Stuart] I know exactly what this is, because I have owned two.
It has two functions.
[Stuart gasps]
[Barry] Wine stopper...
[Stuart] Yeah, it is a wine stopper, it's what it's sold as, and it's called Happy Man.
'Cause I used to get sent them to the P.O. box.
- It will do fizzy, and it will also do wine.
- A fizz stopper and a wine keeper.
[Chris] Uh...There's your second picture. It's not lovely...yes.
[Stuart] Nice. Nice.
[Ryan] Yeah.
[Chris] You quite like the...the twin ring detail?
[Eli] Oh, is it his penis that...extends into the bottle?
[Ryan, Stuart, and Chris] Yeah.
[Eli] Oh. How brilliant.
[Chris] Points all rounds!
[Paul, off-screen] How many?
[Barry] Oh, it's a bottle opener!
[Chris] Two!
[Ryan] His penis is very high up!
[Stuart] That's a different one! That's...that's a separate item.
[Barry] That's a bottle opener. I've never seen that before.
[Chris] I...I would assume you get...
[Eli] It's a bottle opener and a stopper.
[Chris] ...two for your money.
[man whispering] Wish.
[Eli] It's a pollution...
[Eli] It's a pollution...filter for your nose.
[Chris] Okay, anyone else?
[Stuart] I think he's right, actually.
[Chris] Two pollution filters?
[Ryan] I think this is for two bottles to drink and you can re-do fizz in them.
[Barry] Ooh. [sighs]
[Chris] Okay.
[Eli] "Refizzinator".
[Chris] Fizz pump?
[Ryan] Yeah, "refizzinator". Yeah, fizz pump.
[Eli] The Refizzinator.
I am the Refizzinator, and I bring you...fizzy!
[everyone laughing]
[Stuart] Fizzy!
[Eli singing] Two bottles at once!
[Barry] I think it's something like that, 'cause the ribs on the thing...I don't know if the...the nose thing would...I don't know.
[Eli] Let's see! I'm desperate to find out.
[Chris] I've forgotten who said what!
[Chris] It's to...It's actually for snoring, so...
[everyone] Oh!
[Barry] "Stuffy nose breathing apparatus".
[Paul, off-screen] Fifty points for Eli.
[Ryan] Man, you said for pollution and stuff! This is for when you're sleeping.
[Eli] Ah, it doesn't matter what it's for, it's what...you do with it.
[Chris] Well, it kind of does.
[Ryan] Wait, that's the point of the game. It does.
[Barry] How does that work?
[Eli] One point for me.
[Chris] It just opens up...your nostrils.
[Barry] Oh, so when you're sleeping at night, you get better breathing.
[man whispering] Wish.
[Barry] Oh!
[Chris] One of those.
[Barry] Ah...
[Ryan] "HelloDream".
[Ryan] That's...
[Barry] It is...a...toy.
[Stuart] Whoop.
[Stuart] I'm going to chuck my cock and...oh, God, no. I'm putting this bit of cardboard in.
[Eli] Invite the cock into the room.
[Chris laughs]
Yeah. I'm going to chuck my...
- [Stuart] Yeah.
- ...pointy cock in.
[Chris] Don't you want to guess what it is? You've all said, obviously think it's a cock thing...
[Eli] You stick your knob in it and it fellates...your missus.
And...the other bit is for stimulating something inside, I don't know if that's the prostate...
- It goes up your arse.
- [Stuart] Yeah.
- Is it...
[Eli] Goes in your vagina.
[Ryan] You know...you know those things where you stick your fingers...together, and you get stuck in them?
[Stuart] Ooh, like a Chinese finger trap!
Is it one of those, but for a man and a lady?
[Barry] I think it's a vagina in a can.
[Stuart] Yeah.
[Ryan] Oh.
[Eli] Liquid Ass.
[Ryan] But Hello...HelloDream sounds so soft, and tender, and nice! I don't think...
[Stuart] Yeah. They do things like that, especially Chinese pirates.
Yeah. You've got the Tenga Eggs, have you heard of those?
No.
They're like an egg, and you fuck it.
[Chris] I mean, guys...
[Stuart] So, like a normal egg.
[Ryan] Is that a handle to clip it on your belt?
[Stuart] Oh, that'd be great! [with another accent] Hey lads, look at that, I've just bought for you!
[Ryan] Oh, look what I've got!
Fancy Japanese fanny simulator here!
[Stuart] Maybe the top bit is for the lady, but I think that's unlikely, because...
[Eli] I'd have no clue.
[Stuart] You would have to...you wouldn't...
[Stuart] ...have a sex toy for both sexes.
[Barry] That's like a fluffer.
[Stuart] That's pointless.
[Stuart] So, I'm going for...
[Eli] It looks like it's got rabbit ears.
[Stuart and Ryan] Yeah.
[someone off-screen] Answers, please!
[Paul off-screen] Answers!
[Ryan] You know what?
[Chris] Well, I think they are comprehensively answering...
[Ryan] I'm going to say...the sexual equivalent of the finger binding thing, but for a man and a lady.
[Barry] Vagi-pot.
[Eli] I think those ear things inflate inside your bum.
[Paul laughs off-screen]
[Chris] I...I don't want to...
[Barry] Oh!
[Chris] ...say there is...
[Eli] That's about the size of an iPhone.
[Ryan] Is it a phone case?!? Oh, no.
[Chris] It's a fucking flask, guys!
[Barry laughs]
[Stuart] What?!?
[Chris] It's for putting...hot...liquids in.
[Eli] Ah!
[Eli] I could put my dick in that.
[Stuart] Well...
[Chris, whispering] Jesus Christ.
Unfortunately, due to the very wide shape of it, and it looking very short and small...
- How small is that flask? It's that big!
- [Eli] It's quite small, isn't it?
- [Stuart] Yeah!
- You get one Yoplait in it, you're done.
- Yeah!
Don't put your yoghurt in that! It's not for hot yoghurt! [everyone laughs]
- I've got a hot lassi with my name on it.
- [Paul laughs off-screen] The dog!
[everyone laughing]
[Stuart] Oh, my God.
[Chris, appalled] Guys, no points!
[man whispering] Wish.
[Barry] Is that a power button?
[Eli] Penis calibrator.
[Barry] Settings...
[Barry] That is, uh...a lighter.
[Stuart] Oh, God. So, it could be a musical sex toy, ...
[Barry] It actually says "a lighter".
- or it could be...a vape device or something that...
- [Eli] It looks like a vape, doesn't it?
- that's also an MP3 player or something? Umm...
- [Chris] All right.
I would go for...
home...
home...chemical...
home...chemical...tester.
[Paul, off-screen] You just said three words...
[Chris laughs]
[Barry] MP3 player.
[Stuart] Oh, my God! It does look like a DNA sequencer or something if you look at the thing, doesn't it?
[Stuart] Uhh...
[Stuart] Uhh... [imitates race car noise]
[imitates race car changing gears]
[imitates race car brake]
Umm...
[Barry] Settings...
[Stuart] In and Out settings...what?
[Stuart] And brightness.
[Stuart] Hang on!
[Chris] I need an answer.
[Stuart] Brightness, volume, in and out.
[Stuart] Sounds like the Agadoo!
- Umm...it's...it's...it's a vape, most probably a testing device.
- Is it a light that flashes in time with music?
[Chris] All really good answers; unfortunately, that is the sex toy.
[Stuart] Oh! I regret...
[Eli] "Masturbating Cup Hands"...
[Stuart] Should have stuck with it.
[running footsteps]
[Chris laughs]
[Stuart] It is literally a sex toy with a built-in...MP3 player.
[Chris] It's...It's...It's a pocket fanny, you can stick it to a hard surface if you want,
you stick your dick in it...
- ...basically.
- [Stuart] I like the way it says "ULTIMATE PISTON" on the side.
[Chris] What really confused me...
[Stuart] Ohh!
[Eli] Oh, my God.
[Chris] Okay, it heats up. You're going to stick your dick in something that comes from China and it heats up. Fine.
Apparently it's the same size, although bigger than a woman.
Also, it's got a no entry sign on it, when clearly the other picture shows you...
Also, it's got a no entry sign on it, when clearly the other picture shows you...entering it!
- There's...there's a lot about this advert I really don't understand.
- [Eli] "Auto Suck Masturbator".
- I think you're asking for an injury from that thing.
- [Eli] I wouldn't put mine in that.
[Barry] I did it for my Kitchen Gadget Testing there. That's a hot dog cooker! [laughs]
[Eli] Reminds me of that guy who...
[everyone laughs]
[Stuart] Oh, man.
[Eli] ...that guy who, uh...had sex with a Findus Crispy Pancake, he cooked his knob end.
[Barry] Really?
[Eli] Yeah.
[Stuart] Wow.
Some guy fucked a pasty from Greggs, and sued them 'cause it burned his dick.
[Eli] Yeah.
[Chris] Wow.
I'm going to guess the judge didn't rule in his favour.
No, he won.
- What?!?
- No, he didn't.
- Oh, God.
[Stuart clapping lightly]
[Paul, off-screen] Oh.
[everyone clapping]
[Paul] Ryan gets a complementary handjob from me later.
[Barry] With the Wankerchief.
[Chris] "Wankerchief".
[Chris, Barry, and Paul laugh]
[Paul] The patented Wankerchief.
[Chris] So, welcome to Barshens, and this is called "Be Careful What You Wish For"! [rustling]
[someone off-screen] Chris, could you do that again, please? 'Cause you...you've touched your mic.
[Chris] Did I?
[everyone laughing and shouting]
[Chris] Fuck's sake!
[Ryan] IT'S BEEN ON FOR THREE SECONDS!!!
[Paul, off-screen] Fucking hell!
[man whispering] Wish.